<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="TypographyDashes">
    <string name="app_name">Insignia2K16</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_up">SignUp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_global_chat">Global Chat</string>


     <string name="HEX_A_HEX">
        Beware! Dead men tell no tales, neither the one who fails.
        Don’t be fooled by this simplistic name, presenting witch’s game. For all the quiz heads out there,
        we bring you another enchanting bout of quizzing. Insignia 2K16 comes out with span new six genres to ensnare
        your senses. Witness menacing mummies, magnetic moonlight, magic madness manifold.
        Come in teams of two and take aim at the be’WITCH’ing prize that anticipates the winner.
        This isn’t the competition for underprepared. Ready yourself and fare this test and be crowned as the victor.
        The rules here aren’t meant to be bent.
    </string>
    <string name="Les_Quizzerables">
        After the huge success of Thinkquik, the multidisciplinary quiz competition of the first edition,
        here we are with a bigger n better quizzing event ‘Les Quizzerables’.
        You gotta leave no stone unturned to grab the prize that awaits the winner.
        Different genres to choose from and the choice entirely yours.
        You need to prevail three rounds of elimination and the final face off and the glory is all yours.
        This Halloween climb the stairway to heaven with your crazy coven.
        The bylaws are simple and not meant to be disregarded. Brace yourself for this All Hallow’s Eve you need all the spells
        you can memorize to make your opponents’ bones tickle. Savvy a fa’BOOO’lous experience!
    </string>
    <string name="TUSSLE_OF_TONGUES">
        The stage is all set for one big tussle. In fact for a tussle of tongues.
        If you think you have it in you to pull off an argument, then gear up for this mega battle of words.
        All you need to do is to sustain three rounds by giving voice to your thoughts,
        for the one who puts forward his arguments clearly will be the ultimate titan of this clash of clans.
        Here is the description of the rounds
    </string>
    <string name="NITD_MUN">
        A Model United Nations is held so that the participating students, who will roleplay as delegates,
        will learn about international relations between countries and their governments.
        Here in the NITDMUN 2K16 we aim to achieve the very same thing.
        We want our participating delegates to learn about diplomacy between the nations,
        leadership while at the same time participate and showcase their debating skills as well as a plethora of other
        skills which can define a nation’s delegate.
        Our NITD MUN planned to simulate three committees of the United Nations namely the General Assembly,
        Security Council and Human Rights Council. True to the spirit of United Nations, here at NITD MUN,
        we strive to foster constructive forum for open discourse on various global issues.
    </string>
    <string name="WORDSMITHS_WONDERLAND">
        This event will be held in multiple rounds. Four exciting and thrilling rounds have been prepared to engage
        the participants for the duration of the event. A team of two can take part in this event.
        One of the members of the team will compete in the 1st round and the other will compete in the 2nd round.
        1st Round: This is a simple game spanning a total time of two minutes;
        the participants have to write down legitimate words from the English Language starting with a given alphabetical letter.
        2nd Round: This round is a spelling bee, there will be ten words announced over the speakers and the participants have to spell them correctly.
        3rd Round:  It will commence after duration of time. This shall follow a traditional pattern.
        The qualified teams will be provided with a question paper with approx.
        60 questions of varying difficulty. The top 4 teams will move on to the last round. 4th Round:
        It is a rapid fire round where the 4 teams will be divided into groups of 2.
        Group A and B will compete amongst themselves. The winning teams from group ‘A’ and group ‘B’ will compete against each other.
    </string>
    <string name="FOR_BETTER_FOR_VERSE">
        Dive in the depths of your mind to produce a masterpiece as Insignia presents a poem writing competition with a twist.
        The budding poets and poetry enthusiasts are expected to write a poem on a spooky theme, which would be given to them in
        advance, in such a way that the first letter of each line falls in the alphabetical order.
        The top 5 chosen poems must then be recited by the respective participants.
        The best poetry artist would then bag the golden opportunity to win the cash prize.
        This is indeed a call for splendid poems and be there to carve your own masterpiece.
    </string>
    <string name="BLIND_FOLD">
        Have you ever played blindfold games? If no, then here’s your chance to experience it for the first time,
        if yes, then relive those moments here in our fest. This is an individual event in which the participants will be given
        an image to be drawn while blindfolded in 2 minutes. The participants who draw the nearest image will be selected to
        the next round where they will be competing with the other winners of the previous round.
        Finally whoever draws the best picture will win the title of best blindfold artist of Insignia 2K16 and
        a prize of Rs 1000. Isn’t it interesting? Just a couple of minutes to grab thousand bucks!!
        There’s only on spot registration for the event.
    </string>
    <string name="MURRAL_PAINTING">
        Like playing with clay? Then you are at the right place. This event is a test to the creative side in you.
        The participants need to decorate a clay model given to them. Waste material, paints, beads, what not, anything can be used.
        All the participants should do is to give the clay model a life. Sharpen your skills and bring out your episteme.
        This is a team event with each team consisting not more than three members.
    </string>
    <string name="COMES_AROUND_GOES_AROUND">
        What is the fun in winning if there’s no challenge? If you also go by the same philosophy then you would love this event.
        All you have to do is create a story of four paragraphs. Sounds simple, isn’t it? Here comes the twist.
        The given story should be written in such a way that when read backwards, i.e. if the fourth paragraph becomes the first paragraph,
        a different story should be created. This individual event, will truly put your mind to test and challenge your wits.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail_screen">Event Name</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail_events">detail_events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_instafeed">Instafeed</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">NIT DELHI</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_insignia">AboutInsignia</string>

    <string name="invitation_title">Insignia</string>
    <string name="invitation_message">check this out</string>
    <string name="invitation_cta">Install!</string>

    <string name="invitation_custom_image">https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-19/s150x150/13658302_891675384294829_1143366670_a.jpg</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="venue">Venue :</string>
    <string name="title_activity_locate">NIT DELHI</string>
    <string name="address">National Institute of Technology Delhi\n Institute of Applied Manpower Research (IAMR Campus)\n A-7, Institutional Area\n Near Satyawadi Raja Harish Chandra Hospital,\n Narela, Delhi – 110040</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_fest">about_fest</string>


</resources>
